Love will find us all.
Entergalactic is a animation, romance, music film directed by Fletcher Moules.
Ambitious artist Jabari attempts to balance success and love when he moves into
his dream Manhattan apartment and falls for his next-door neighbor.
Jabari (voice), played by Kid Cudi.
Meadow Watson (voice), played by Jessica Williams.
Carmen Atkins (voice), played by Laura Harrier.
Ky (voice), played by Ty Dolla Sign.
Jimmy (voice), played by Timothée Chalamet.
Karina (voice), played by Vanessa Hudgens.
Entergalactic (stylized in all caps) is a 2022 adult animated musical romantic comedy television special created by
American musician and actor Kid Cudi, that serves as a visual companion piece to the album of the same name.
Initially announced as a television series, in August 2022,
Entergalactic was then redeveloped as a TV special.
The special premiered on September 30, 2022, exclusively
on Netflix, simultaneously with the album.
Directed by Fletcher Moules, it is based on the album, which
Cudi recorded before storyboarding the TV special.
Alongside Cudi, it stars the voices of Jessica Williams, Timothée Chalamet, Ty Dolla Sign, Laura Harrier, Vanessa Hudgens,
Christopher Abbott, 070 Shake, Teyana Taylor, Jaden Smith, Keith David, Arturo Castro, and Macaulay Culkin.
Entergalactic uses an art style inspired by that of I Lost
My Body (2019) and When Harry Met Sally...
Billed as a "television event", it received critical acclaim for
its animation, visual style, music, and story.
Entergalactic is dedicated to Cudi's deceased friend, American fashion designer Virgil Abloh, who served as a costume
designer on the project before his death, with the release date coinciding with Abloh's birth date.
The film explores themes of new york city,
photographer, ex-girlfriend, artist, graffiti.
The tone is emotional.